原创翻译  双语字幕
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
"致所有真正的自由之子
"To all true Children of Liberty,
我们相信这个国家属于我们
who believe this country is ours.
我们必须抵制外星人灾害"
We must resist the alien scourge."
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
如果那些人是因为害怕低人一等
If people feeling inferior is what makes them
才加入仇恨组织
join these hate groups,
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
那我们就让他们公平竞争
then we could just level the playing field.
是哈伦·艾尔造成的吗
Did the Harun-El do this?
哈伦让心脏坚不可摧
It made the heart invincible.
校对     肉松  饿得慌
我想推进哈伦·艾尔协议
I want to move forward with the Harun-El protocol.
我们需要进行人体实验
We're gonna need a human subject.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
他们夺走了我的宝贝
They took my baby, man.
对不起  小菲  我得按我的方式去做
Sorry, Fi. I've got to do it my way.
后期     你是不是饿得慌
我联络上了真正的自由之子
I got connected with some Children of Liberty.
汤姆  很高兴认识你
Tom, nice to meet you, bro.
我没法直接接触到自由代表
I don't have direct access to Agent Liberty.
总监     你是不是饿得慌
不过我可以帮你牵线
But I can connect you with people who do.
所有单位着手处理
All units respond to a hostage situation
外星裂变棒工厂的人质事件
at the alien fission rod factory.
放下枪  趴在地上
Lower your gun and get down on the ground.
否则我不敢保证你能活着走出去
Or I can't promise you'll walk out of here.
你们现在安全了
You're safe now.
干得好
Good job.
你的搭档们想拿裂变棒干什么
So what did your partners want with the fission rods?
把你告诉我的再跟她讲一遍
Go ahead, tell her what you told me.
我什么都不知道
I don't know anything.
我们不用武力解决问题
Hey, hey, that is not how we do things.
反正你都要被警察带走
Look, you're getting in the back of a police car anyway
就告诉我们实情吧
so just tell us the truth.
我发誓我真的不知道
I swear I don't know any more.
我说想帮忙  他们给了我两个选择
I said I wanted to help and they gave me two options.
要么过来偷裂变棒
I could show up here and steal some fission rods,
要么就等船舶货运送达
or hang out, waiting for some cargo shipment.
我们问完了
We're done here.
搭档  等等
Hey, partner. Wait up.
我很感谢你的付出
Look, I appreciate what you're doing,
接下来交给我就好
but I can take it from here.
自由代表夺走了我的一切
Look, Agent Liberty took everything from me.
我要竭尽全力将他绳之于法
I will do anything to see him brought to justice. Anything.
让我帮忙吧  我很聪明
Just let me help. I'm resourceful.
我追踪到了他们  不是吗
I tracked them here, didn't I?
我找到线索会给你打电话
I'll call you if I find anything.
抱歉蒙了你的眼
I apologize for the blindfold.
这是为了防止你逃跑  你明白的
A necessary precaution, you understand.
我懂
Yeah, I get it.
但我对你没有威胁
But I'm no threat to you.
我是自己来的
I came here on my own accord.
来跟你谈谈
To talk to you.
听听你这边的说法
To listen. I'm prepared to hear your side of the story.
你显然有自己的计划  但为什么要这么做
I mean, obviously, you have an agenda, but why?
一定有原因
There has to be something.
你遭遇的某件事情  激起了你的愤怒
The core of your anger, something that's happened to you.
我确实遭遇过某件事情  奥尔森先生
Something did happen to me, Mr. Olsen.
我看到人们努力跟上时代
I saw men struggling to remain relevant,
养家糊口
to provide for their family,
我看到人类遭到了不公的待遇
I saw human beings being treated less than they deserve.
失去了优越性
Less than exceptional.
我相信你内心的某一部分
Surely, there has to be a part of you
能找到外星人和人类的共同性
that can find a commonality between aliens and humans.
我们只希望心爱的人
We just want good, safe lives
能过上安稳的好日子
for our loved ones.
不  我们要谈的并不是我对外星人
No, we're not here to talk about my empathy,
缺乏同情心的问题
or lack thereof, for aliens.
那你来告诉我
Okay, you tell me.
你想让我报道什么
What am I writing?
你什么都不必报道
You won't be writing anything.
我这是给你一个机会
I'm giving you an opportunity
出现在镜头前
to step in front of the camera for once,
成为焦点  激励鼓舞大家
to be the story, to galvanize and to inspire.
因为守护者
Because Guardian
代表着我的追随者们为之奋斗的一切
stands for everything that my followers strive for.
人类例外主义
Human exceptionalism.
你想让我鼓舞你的追随者
You want me to inspire your followers?
你想让我怎么做
And how exactly do you want me to do that?
我想让你毁掉一样东西
I want you to destroy something.
一座纪念碑
A monument,
它与我们的信仰背道而驰
something that stands against everything we believe in.
我不会破坏东西
I don't tear things down.
那不是我的作风
That's not my style.
我懂  你现在还不想参与进来
I get it, you're not a willing participant yet.
但你将来会的
But you will be.
我相信你  奥尔森先生
I believe in you, Mr. Olsen.
裂变棒刚刚送到了
The fission rods were just delivered.
其余的呢  都准备好了吗
What about the rest? It's set?
-是的  -很好
- Yeah. - Good.
那我们可以替感恩节失去的兄弟们报仇了
Then the men we lost on Thanksgiving will be avenged.
明晚
And by tomorrow night,
超女就会死掉
Supergirl will be dead.
超 女
第四季 第七集
卢瑟小姐  实验对象来了
Miss Luthor, the subject's here.
-他来早了  -他迫不及待开始实验了
- He's early. - Well, he's eager to get started.
他人很好
He's a real nice guy.
有一双漂亮的墨绿色眼睛  像你一样
He's got nice green eyes, like yours.
伊芙  针对人类实验对象
Eve, doing experiments of this nature
进行这类实验  是极其严肃的事情
on a human subject is extremely serious.
我一直犹豫是否要继续
I've had qualms about even proceeding.
你这样是在帮倒忙
You are not making this any easier.
实在抱歉
I'm so sorry.
当然了  你一定要继续
Of course. You have to proceed.
我表姐进了临终关怀中心
My cousin's in hospice.
癌症转移了  她有两个小女儿
Metastasized cancer, she's got two little girls.
你救回了那两个孩子的母亲
You give those kids their mother back
如果实验成功  你还将拯救更多的家庭
and just imagine all the other families that you'd rescue.
甚至拯救我们的国家
Not to mention saving our country.
如果你让人类也拥有了超能力
If you level the playing field and make humans super,
就能阻止又一场内战
you could be preventing another civil war.
你为实验对象做好准备了吗
Have you prepared the subject?
是的  他名叫...
Yes. His name--
不  别告诉我他的名字
No. No, don't tell me his name.
我们就称他为实验对象0331
We'll refer to him as subject 0331.
你肯定就是实验技术员了
Well, you must be the lab tech.
我是你的小白鼠  我叫...
I'm your rat. Name's--
实验对象0331  男性
Subject 0331, male,
棕发  绿眼  身高约1米75
brown hair, green eyes, approximately 5'9".
左后胁有76毫米长的伤疤
Three-inch scar on the left rear flank.
玩冰球受的伤
Hockey injury.
我们水牛城的小伙子在冰上特别能闹
Buffalo boys. Can't trust us on the ice.
我想你在签下合约前
I assume you've read and considered
已经阅读并考虑过实验条件了
the conditions of the experiment before you signed the contract.
你想再看看的话  请随意
Feel free to look it over,
但我需要你输入指纹来使合约生效
but I will need your thumbprint to make it binding.
等等  你口中的条件是指这部分  对吗
Yeah, wait, by conditions, you mean this part, right?
"我  实验对象
"I, the subject,
理解并知晓实验的全部风险
understand and acknowledge the full range of risks
包括但不限于
including, but not limited to
15%终结的可能性"
a 15% chance of expiration."
"终结"就是死亡的意思  对吗  技术员
"Expiration" As in death, right, lab tech?
说得我会像牛奶一样过期似的
That makes me sound like a carton of milk.
假如条款令你不适
If you're uncomfortable with the terms,
你大可换衣服走人
you can just get dressed and leave.
不不不  我只是逗你玩
No, no, no. I'm just messing with you.
我当然理解条款  只不过
Of course, I understand the terms. It's just...
为什么说得这么隐晦
Why the soft-pedaling?
就像所有人总是说
I mean, it's kind of like when everyone would say,
"我很遗憾你哥哥过世了"
"I'm so sorry your brother passed."
过什么  过气[放屁]吗
Passed what, gas?
过了驾驶考试吗
Passed his driver's test?
不  他不是过世了  女士  他死了
No, he didn't pass, lady. He freaking died.
死了  死翘翘了
Dead, as in a doornail.
我跑题了  我总这样  我完全同意
Anyways, I digress. It's a thing I do. I'm totally in.
这就按指纹
Here is my thumbprint.
请抬起手臂好吗
Can I see your arm, please?
那就左臂吧
I suggest my left.
这项实验的启事特别强调
The ad for this gig made a pretty big deal
整个实验都要保密
of secrecy of the whole thing.
但鉴于我在拿自己的性命冒险
But, uh, seeing as how I'm putting my life on the line,
我想知道实验的目的
well, I'd love to know what it's for.
你肯定和这个科学家很熟  对吗
Well, you must know the scientist pretty well, right?
你能告诉我他想干什么吗
Can you tell me what he's up to?
是为了科学进步
It's the advancement of science.
你真难搞
You're tough.
但你冰冷的面孔下也是肉做的心
But under all that ice, there's a heart.
我看得出来
I can tell.
我到底能不能见到这位幕后领导者
So will I ever get to meet the man behind all this?
你已经见过他了  我就是科学家
You have met him. I'm the scientist.
你得看看这个
Hey, I have to show you something.
好  等一下
Okay, in a minute.
布莱尼  我需要你追踪
Brainy, I need you to track--
失踪的外星裂变棒  已经在追踪了
Missing alien fission rods? Already on it.
很好  我还需要你追踪任何可疑的船舶货...
Great. And I need to track any rogue cargo ship--
你们正在收看的是本·洛克伍德的《锁定》
...you are watching The Lockdown with Ben Lockwood.
那个人怎么做起电视节目了
What is that man doing on TV?
我说了你得看看这个
I told you I needed to show you something.
我很遗憾地说
And I'm sorry to say
今晚的节目会在阴郁的气氛下开始
we're going to start tonight's show on a very somber note.
因为在感恩节之夜
Because on Thanksgiving night,
五位和平抗议外星人接管母星的人
five men peacefully protesting the alien takeover
至今行踪不明
of their home planet went missing.
蟑螂们认为他们可以随时随地
Roaches think they can blow us out of the water
突袭我们
whenever they want.
他们见到超女飞来飞去  围捕无辜的人
They see Supergirl flying around, rounding up innocent people.
他们居然怪我
They're blaming me!
超女是英雄吗
Is Supergirl a hero,
还是说正是她这颗种子
or is she the seed that may very well
引发了人类的灭亡
'cause the eradication of the human race?
什么
What?
你在感恩节救了上百个人
Hey, you saved hundreds of people on Thanksgiving.
我们甚至不知道失踪事件是否和外星人有关
And we don't even know if aliens were involved in the disappearances.
我们还在调查
We're still investigating.
等等
Hang on.
荣恩  出什么事了
J'onn, what's happening?
曼彻斯特·布莱克刚刚给我来过电话
Hi, I just got a call from Manchester Black,
他说你们俩之前在调查某件事
said you two were working on something?
他想让我给你传个口信
He wanted me to give you a message.
关于船舶货运的
Something about a cargo shipping.
真的吗  把细节发给我
Really? Send me the details.
这就发
Will do.
汤姆
Tom?
我很抱歉把你牵扯进来
I'm so sorry I got you involved in all this.
他们骗了我
They lied to me.
我以为他们只是想采访你
I thought they were gonna give you an interview.
我不知道他们会利用你
I didn't know they were gonna use you.
我的护手
My gauntlet.
快来  我们时间不多
Come on, we don't have a lot of time.
欢迎来到地球
Welcome to Earth.
你接下来将办理移民手续
You are about to be processed for immigration.
这座岛会抑制你的能力
The island will dampen your powers,
但请放心  离岛后能力会立即恢复
but rest assured, they'll return as soon as you leave.
地球是个友好的地方
Earth is a friendly place,
你在这里很安全
you are safe here.
欢迎来到雪莱岛
Welcome to Shelley Island.
雪莱岛
Shelley Island?
我以为马斯丁总统辞职后
I thought this place was shut down
这地方已经关闭了
after President Marsdin resigned.
是的  所以正义之子在这里集会
It was. That's why it's the perfect place
再适合不过
for the Children of Liberty to gather.
詹姆斯·奥尔森逃跑了  搜索全岛
James Olsen has escaped. Search the island.
禁止所有船只靠岸或离岸
No boats on or off.
快  船在这边
Come on, the boat's this way.
快跑  詹姆斯  快跑
Go! James, go!
快跑
Go!
地球的叛徒
Earth traitor.
住手  住手  等等
Stop, stop, stop. Wait, wait, wait!
你们想让我做什么都可以
I'll do whatever you want.
不要伤害他
Just don't hurt him.
看到没
You see?
我就知道你会接受召唤
I knew you'd heed the call.
谢谢你的线索
Thanks for the tip.
你破解出了什么密码
So what's this code you've cracked?
跟我来
Follow me.
我发现能源工程的那个卑鄙小人
Once I realized that little weasel in the energy factory
给了我们所需的一切信息  剩下的就很容易了
gave us everything we needed, the rest was easy.
链路协议标志
DISL label.
货运集装箱的国际标准识别码
International standard codes for ID and freight containers.
我从船厂工头那偷走了记录
I nicked the logs from the shipyard foreman,
做了交叉比对
did a little cross-referencing
发现了这个意外收获
and found our prize.
那我们看看一号门后面有些什么吧
So, shall we see what's behind door number one?
是空的
It's empty.
温度还很低
And freezing.
不管运的是什么  温度一直保持在零下
Whatever was shipped in here was kept at sub-zero.
现在却消失得无影无踪了
Yeah, now it's gone without a trace.
也许有迹可循
Maybe not.
是运输标签的一部分
It's part of a shipping label.
曼彻斯特
Manchester?
最好把我想知道的都告诉我
You better tell me what I need to know.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
他是这里的监管员
He's the supervisor.
他肯定知道货物运去哪里了
He must know where that shipment was headed.
-货物运去哪了  -住手
- Where did it go? - Stop!
住手  你不能以暴力威逼
Stop, he can't speak through your fist.
这下好了  他要去报警了
Well done. Now he's gonna go call the cops.
我不在乎
I don't care.
你有可能把他的下巴打骨折
You could've broken his jaw.
我们不能伤害无辜的人  你怎么回事
We don't hurt innocent people. What is wrong with you?
对不起  有时我只是有点...
Okay, look, sorry. Sometimes I just get a little...
过去两个月我过得很艰难
I had a rough couple of months.
也许你应该再休息几个月  缓一缓
Yeah, well, maybe you should take a few more and cool down.
我说了对不起
I said I was sorry.
来这里是个错误
This was a mistake.
什么
What?
不得不说  我很惊讶你还没赶我走
I've gotta say I'm surprised you haven't kicked me out yet.
为什么赶你走
For what?
假设科学家是男性
Assuming the scientist was a man.
我的教养没那么差  抱歉
I was raised better than that. Sorry.
我接受你的道歉
Apology accepted.
你能至少告诉我你的名字吗
Can you at least tell me your name?
博士
Doctor...
基兰
Kieran.
基兰博士
Dr. Kieran.
我猜你其他的小白鼠
I'll bet your other lab rats
没有这样得罪你吧  基兰博士
haven't offended you this much, Dr. Kieran.
要得罪我没这么容易
I don't offend easily.
这里也没有其他实验对象
And there are no other subjects.
什么
What?
只有我一个人吗
I'm the only one?
没错
That's right.
我是唯一献身于
What, was I the only one crazy enough
未知事业的疯子吗
to risk my life for something unknown?
在一百多名申请者中
Out of over 100 applicants,
只有十二人能接受这些风险
all but 12 were acceptably risk-tolerant.
好吧  但你为什么选中我
Okay. But why did you pick me?
我有我的理由
I have my reasons.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
基博士  从来没人选我做任何事
Dr. K, I have never been picked for anything.
所以你必须要告诉我
So you have to tell me.
哲学家内格尔的蜘蛛浴室谜题
Nagel's spider in the shower conundrum.
蜘蛛谜题吗
The spider thing?
那是个多选题
That was a multiple choice question.
浴室里有只蜘蛛
There's a spider in a shower,
它已经困在那里好几天
and it's been there for days, trapped.
每次你一开水
And every time you turn the water on,
蜘蛛就会拼命逃跑  但是它却逃不出去
it tries to run for its life to escape, but it can't get out.
你会怎么办
So what do you do?
把蜘蛛放生到安全的地方  还是杀了它
Do you move it to safety, do you kill it?
什么也不做  你不知道蜘蛛想要什么
Nothing. You don't know what the spider wants.
就不要去管它
You leave it the hell alone.
没错
Yeah.
只有我一个人选C吗
Was I the only one who picked C?
还有我
Other than me.
好吧  所以你选我
Okay. So you picked me
是因为我不在乎蜘蛛的死活吗
because I don't care whether a spider lives or dies.
如果实验成功了  我最不想要的就是英雄
If this thing works, the last thing I want is a hero.
那你大可放心
Then you have nothing to worry about.
我的哥哥
My brother,
过世的那位
the one who passed,
他以前是个英雄
he was a hero.
他简直完美到令人作呕
He was so perfect it could be nauseating.
相信我  我从来都不是个英雄
Believe me, I've never been a hero.
我也不是
Neither have I.
你失去过什么人吧  基博士
You ever lost someone, Dr. K?
是的
Yeah.
她是我唯一的英雄
She was the only hero I ever had.
天呐
Oh, my.
火鸡应该不能重复加热四次吧
I don't think you can cook a turkey four different times.
这样更入味
It's accumulating flavor.
好吧
Yeah.
布莱尼在我来的路上打给我
Listen, Brainy called on my way over here.
他还在检测
He's still running tests on the label
你从船厂带回来的标签
that you brought back from the shipyard.
但是他们找到了自由之子的失踪尸体
But they did find the missing bodies of the Children of Liberty.
没有证据显示是外星人所为
And there was no evidence they were killed by aliens.
但是
But,
这是私人仇怨
this was personal.
头骨断裂  下颌骨折  还有枪伤
Busted skulls, broke jaws, in addition to gunshot wounds.
下颌骨折
Broken jaws.
你觉得指节铜环能造成这种损伤吗
Do you think brass knuckles could cause that much damage?
如果使用者的手臂足够强壮的话  可以的
If they're paired with a strong enough arm, yeah.
我想你也许会再加热火鸡  所以我带了鸡翅来
I, uh, thought you might be re-heating, so I brought wings.
-不是吧  -感谢上帝
- Oh, come on. - Thank God.
无意冒犯
Uh, no offense.
已经冒犯到了
Offense taken.
我在酒吧买晚餐的时候见到了曼彻斯特
I, uh, saw Manchester at the bar when I was grabbing dinner.
他让我向你转达他的歉意
He wanted me to tell you how sorry he was.
荣恩  你曾说曼彻斯特跟你一样崇尚和平
J'onn, you told me Manchester was on the path of peace, like you.
我们确实有着同样的挣扎
We share a similar struggle, yeah.
所以我很能理解
So I understand how much
他希望自己能够做出贡献
he wants to feel like he's doing something.
我也能明白  他想控制自己的暴力冲动
And how hard it is for him to resist his more
有多难
violent urges.
你觉得他会不会
You don't think he's capable
杀了五个自由之子呢
of killing five Children of Liberty, do you?
他确实很愤怒
He is angry.
但在愤怒之下  他经受着痛苦的煎熬
But under that anger is just a lot of pain.
菲奥娜的死让他崩溃
Fiona's death just rocked him.
曼彻斯特有一颗善良的心
Manchester has a good heart.
我不想就这样放弃他
I'm not ready to give up on him just yet.
每一次的抗争他都帮了我
I mean, he's been on my side every step of the fight.
他很聪明  也很固执
He's resourceful and stubborn.
如果他有什么目标  就会不懈努力
And if he wants something he'll go after it.
他能帮上忙
He could be useful.
好
Okay.
超女
Supergirl.
你不是不想跟我有瓜葛吗
I thought you wanted nothing to do with me.
对
Yeah.
但我跟荣恩谈了谈
But I spoke to J'onn,
他说我应该再给你一次机会
and he said I should give you another chance.
这是菜肉馅饼  算是和解礼物
It's a pot pie. It comes in peace.
谢谢
Thank you.
我没能亲眼见到菲奥娜
I never got the chance to meet Fiona.
但荣恩说她人很好
But J'onn tells me she was remarkable.
确实
She was.
我知道你想为她主持公道
I know you want justice for her.
我希望能够帮你
I wanna help you find that.
-超女  -稍等
- Supergirl. - Just a second.
布莱尼  什么事
Brainy, what is it?
集装箱里的东西有线索了吗
Did we get a hit on the contents of the container?
标签本身损毁严重  无法解读
The label itself was too destroyed to interpret.
但我分析了上面的残留物  80%是胶
But I found the residue on it to be 80% glue
9.73%是墨
and 9.73% ink.
其余是纳尔赛特
The rest was Nalcyite.
是什么东西  危险吗
What is that? Is it dangerous?
是纳尔赛星的盐
It's Nalcian table salt.
但是在地球  它很容易挥发
However, on Earth, it could be quite volatile.
在正确的条件下  每克纳尔赛特中的爆炸物
Under the right conditions, it has an explosive factor
可释放8000焦耳能量
of 8,000 joules per gram,
也可以造成小型精准核武器的爆炸效果
or that of a tiny, precise nuclear explosion.
我得回超查部了
I should get back to the DEO.
等等  超查部已经在查那颗炸弹了
No, wait. The DEO is already on it looking for that bomb.
也许我们可以自己做一些调查
So maybe you and I can crack something here.
你的朋友说有发现会联系你  对吧
Your friend said he'll call if he finds something, right?
对  是的
Right. Yeah.
给
Here.
要来点吗
Want some?
谢谢
Thank you.
你到底有没有打算告诉我
So are you ever actually gonna tell me
我们到底要做什么
what it is we're doing here?
如果成功  但愿如此  我希望你知道
In success, which I'm counting on, you'll need to know.
我们计划治愈一切疾病
We're attempting to cure everything.
比如癌症吗
Like cancer?
一切让人类软弱的疾病
Everything that makes men weak.
你的意思是  如果一年前有这一切
Are you telling me if this had happened a year ago,
我哥哥可能还活着吗
that my brother might still be here?
不止如此
Not only that,
如果成功了
but if this works,
我们不仅能修复人类的不足  你还会...
we'll cure not only all human ailments, but you'll get...
拥有能力
Abilities.
什么  超能力吗
What, like superpowers?
类似吧
Something like that.
但你不想创造英雄
But you didn't want a hero.
我想找一个有责任感的人
I wanted someone responsible.
而不是觉得自己有超能力
Somebody who wouldn't think that
就自以为知道什么是最好的
they knew what was best just because they had powers.
我觉得这样不好
I don't think this is a good idea.
我不是好人
I'm not a good person.
关于我的疤痕  我说了谎
You know, I lied to you about my scar?
不是冰球棒弄伤的
Yeah, it's not from a hockey stick.
似乎是手术创伤  也许是肾脏移植
Looks like a surgical incision. Maybe from a kidney transplant?
那颗肾脏就是我无私哥哥的死因
That kidney is the reason my perfect selfless brother is dead.
我需要肾脏  他自愿捐献
I needed a kidney and he volunteered.
整件事情本来是常规手术
And the whole thing was supposed to be routine,
但是他为了救我  死在了手术台上
but he died on the operating table to save me.
你知道最糟糕的事是什么吗
You know what the worst part is?
如果角色互换
If the roles had been reversed,
我绝对不会把肾脏给他
I wouldn't have given him my freaking kidney!
不可能的  因为我太自私了
No way! I was too selfish.
当时是我生了病  本来应该是我死的
I was the one dying, I am the one who's supposed to be dead!
所以你才报名吗
Is that why you signed up?
因为你不在乎自己能否活下来
Because you don't care if you're gonna live or die?
听我说  基博士
Um, look, Dr. K,
你显然在做一件很伟大的事
you're obviously doing something great here,
我不希望给你添乱
and I don't wanna mess this up for you.
你曾说这项技术可以拯救  几百万人吗
I mean, you said that this could save, what, millions?
几亿人  是几亿人
Hundreds. Hundreds of millions.
好  但我是个扫把星
Yeah, well, everything I touch is cursed.
如果你改变了心意
If you've had a change of heart
想要退出这次实验  那...
and you wanna drop back, that's...
-那也没问题  -不是这样的
- That's okay. - That's not it at all.
你应该找个比我强的人来帮助你
You deserve someone way better than me to help you achieve this.
我从一百名申请者中选了你
Out of 100 applicants, I chose you.
如果你选错了呢
What if you chose wrong?
我很聪明
Well, I'm a very smart woman.
我坚持我的选择
I stand by my choice.
我错得太离谱了
I was so wrong.
我以为加入了自由之子
I thought if I joined the Children of Liberty
-我就不会这么...  -无助吗
- I wouldn't feel so... - Helpless?
看来受恐惧指引  就会造成这样的后果
I guess this is what happens when we let fear guide us.
是啊
Yeah.
我们都做了很多选择  才走到这一步
We both made choices that got us here, right?
我找过你帮忙
I mean, I asked you for help.
不  如果你留下
No. If you stay,
如果你炸掉纪念碑
if you blow up that monument
大家会觉得你支持他们
then everyone's gonna think you're with them.
你是自由之子
That you're a Child of Liberty.
你能让他们有脸面  有合理性
You're gonna give them the face they've been dying for,
这是他们梦寐以求的
the legitimacy.
那又怎样
So what?
如果我留下  结果就是这样
That's what happens if I stay.
但我如果走了  保住了名誉
But if I go and I preserve my reputation,
你就会死
you die.
然后怎样呢  汤姆  我不懂
And then what, Tom? I'm lost.
你会死
And you're dead.
那我就不比他好多少
And then I am no better than him.
而我远比那样要强
And I'm stronger than that.
我这辈子
I have spent my entire life
都在把自己塑造成今天的模样
building myself up into the man that I am today
我没有给这个社会质疑我的理由
and I have not given society one reason to doubt me.
可名誉算什么
But what is reputation?
名誉是什么  什么都不是
I mean, what is it? It's nothing.
它不能代表你
It's not who you are.
所以如果最新的边缘团体想毁掉纪念碑
So if the latest fringe group wants to tear that monument down,
我们就重建一个
we will build it right back up.
自由代表可以对我的名誉为所欲为
Agent Liberty can do whatever he wants with my reputation.
我知道我是谁
I know who I am.
我总想不通这个问题
I keep coming across this problem.
我们到的时候集装箱是空的
The container was empty when we got to it,
所以他们肯定在别的地方卸了货
which means they had to get rid of the cargo somewhere.
但记录上写着货物刚到
But the logs say the shipment just arrived.
他们来不及在那里卸货
They didn't have time to unload there
或者在别的码头停靠
or to make land at any other docks.
至少在大陆上不可能
At least not on the mainland.
他们肯定在某个岛屿停过  只有这一个可能
They had to have stopped at an island. That's the only way.
失踪的外星裂变棒...
The missing alien fission rods...
他们在雪莱岛
They're on Shelley Island.
小菲就是从那来的
That's where Fi came through.
我以为那里已经荒废了
I thought it was defunct.
没错  但那里是靠外星裂变棒运转的
It was, but it runs on alien fission rods,
就是被偷走的那种裂变棒
just like the ones that were stolen.
他们让岛重新运转了
They turned the island back on.
我必须通知超查部
I have to alert the DEO.
等等  如果这是他们的大本营
Wait. Hey, look, if this is their home base,
而且他们有密谋  那自由代表肯定在那里
and they're planning something, Agent Liberty will be there.
没错  所以我们需要后备力量
Exactly. That's why we need backup.
不  所以我们需要聪明一点
No, it's why we need to be smart.
他那种人  超查部在一英里外他就发现了
A guy like that can smell the DEO a mile away.
我们冲进去  他就会触发开关  或者更糟
If we go in blazing, he'll hit the trigger, or worse.
我们要偷溜进去
We need to sneak in on the hush.
不带大型武器
No big guns. You know,
按你的方式
your way.
好
Okay.
但岛上有超能力阻尼电缆塔
But there are power-dampening pylons on the island.
我们一定要小心  不过幸好
We have to be careful. But luckily,
我总是有备而来
I always come prepared.
这个黄太阳手榴弹可以增强我的超能力
It's a yellow sun grenade to boost my powers.
就像氪星人的多种维生素剂
Think of it like a Kryptonian multivitamin.
我可以看看吗
Can I see that?
可以
Yeah.
厉害
Brilliant.
我就知道跟你合作是对的
I knew I'd do right teaming up with you.
好美
It's beautiful.
你应该看看
Yeah. You should've seen this place
它全面运行时的样子
when it was fully operational.
那里有超能力阻尼器
There's the power dampeners.
不许动
Stay where you are!
抱歉  超女  我发现了一个机会
Sorry, Supergirl. I saw an opportunity.
我的新搭档承诺让我跟头领见面
My new mates here promised me an audience with their king.
所以我答应了他们
So I delivered.
你给我设套
You set me up?
你一直都在耍我  为什么
All this time, you were playing me? Why?
痛苦是强大的动力
Pain is a great motivator.
我说过我什么都做得出来
I told you I'd do anything.
你就是考德威尔吧
You must be Caldwell.
佩特赛利说我可以信任你
Petrocelli said I could trust you.
把超女带来
You get us Supergirl
你就能见老大
and you get to meet the boss.
各位  你们懂的  这个得合理
All right, gentlemen, you know the deal. This has to look legit.
靠近超女前  不要触动开关
And, you, don't pull the trigger until we're near her.
那好  用小强的话说
All right then, as the roaches say,
"带我去见你们的首领"
"Take me to your leader."
耐心点  他很快就到
Have patience. He'll be here soon.
艾丽克斯  艾丽克斯  听得见我说话吗
Alex. Alex, can you hear me?
左臂
Left arm.
又把我当成编号对待了
Back to treating me like a number.
你应该终于知道你的办法错在哪了吧
I guess you've finally seen the error of your ways.
我不配在这里
I don't deserve to be here.
你不是坏人  亚当
You're not a bad person, Adam.
你叫我亚当
You called me "Adam."
你哥哥的死也不是你的错
You're also not responsible for your brother's death.
手术台上的意外
There are hundreds of things that could've caused
可能有很多因素
what happened on that operating table.
但我们知道  至少这事不怪你
We know one thing that wasn't responsible, and that's you.
不是你造成的  你也阻止不了
You didn't cause it, you couldn't have stopped it.
只是坏运气罢了
It was just bad luck.
坏运气不会让你变成坏人
Bad luck doesn't make you a bad person.
坏的决定才会
Bad choices do.
这道理我懂  是因为我这个人远比你糟糕
And I would know because I'm a much worse person than you.
是因为你失去的人吗
Is this about the person you lost?
她是谁
Who was she?
我母亲
My mother.
是我的生母  我养母还生龙活虎的
My real one, not my adoptive, who is very much alive and kicking.
她去世时你多大
How old were you?
四岁
Four.
你不需要告诉我发生了什么
You don't have to tell me what happened.
不  是时候了  我想说
No, I know. It's time. I want to.
她说我们当时在拜访亲人
We were visiting family she said.
在水边  应该是湖边
Somewhere by the water, a lake I think.
湖水...
It was...
湖水很绿
It was so green.
那天并不晴朗  天很阴沉
It wasn't a very bright day, it was overcast,
但我妈说魔法就在那里
but my mom said that's where the magic was.
是雨造就了绿色
It was the rain that made the green.
当然了  她去游泳了
So of course, she went swimming.
没有回来
She didn't come back.
-很抱歉  -不
- I'm sorry. - No.
我当时就在那里
See, I was there.
我就在岸边
I was with her on the shore,
她下水的时候
when she went in,
她溺水的时候  我什么都没做
and when she went under and I did nothing.
我没有跑  我没有哭
I didn't run, I didn't cry.
我只是站在那里
I just stood there.
你那时只有四岁
You were four.
哪有孩子这种时候不会跑向他们妈妈
What kind of child doesn't run to their mother
或是尖叫求救呢
or doesn't scream for help?
我知道
I knew.
我知道不对劲
I knew something was wrong,
但是我什么都没做  我看着她去死了
but I did nothing. I just watched her die.
后来  我被带到了
And afterward, I was brought to this
这个糟糕的家庭
terrible family.
我花了这一生
And I have spent my life
拨乱反正
fighting their legacy,
打击他们的罪行
and their crimes and their evil deeds,
但我始终知道...
but I've always know that...
内心深处
That deep down inside,
我是他们中的一员
that I belonged with them.
休息会儿吧
Get some rest.
今晚  人类英雄守护者
Tonight, the human hero Guardian
发誓效忠于人类
pledged his allegiance to humanity
同时  他毁掉了
as he exterminated
外星人骄傲的象征  还消灭了最强大的对手...
not only the symbol of alien pride, but the greatest adversary...
"但对我们的生存
"But the greatest threat
最大的威胁是
to our survival,
超女"
Supergirl."
记住  如果你说了任何计划之外的话
Remember, if you say anything off-book,
如果你对着镜头皱了眉
if you so much as frown at the camera,
-我不会犹豫的  -我知道规矩
- I will not hesitate-- -I know the rules.
你确定那个纪念碑里没有人吗
And you're sure that there's no one in that monument?
我发誓
Cross my heart.
现在站在雷管前  然后说"茄子"
Now stand in front of the detonator and say "Cheese."
微小而精确的核爆炸
Tiny, precise nuclear explosion.
我一直在考虑去大西洋彼岸开启新篇章
So, I've been thinking about starting a chapter across the pond.
你知道  英国之子
You know, Children of Britain.
我们到了
Here we are.
进来吧
Come on in.
五分钟  洛克伍德先生
Five minutes, Mr. Lockwood.
没错
You got it.
布莱克先生
Mr. Black.
久闻你的大名
I've heard a lot about you.
拜托
Please,
我们来谈谈吧
let's talk.
好的  来吧
Yes, let's.
我叫詹姆斯·奥尔森
My name is James Olsen.
我信任自由之子
And I believe in the Children of Liberty,
还有他们支持的一切
and everything they stand for.
只有人类
Only humans
属于地球
belong on Earth.
詹姆斯
James!
设备联机
Device online.
詹姆斯
James!
设备激活
Device activated.
詹姆斯
James!
我听说你想讨论向欧洲扩展
I hear you wanna discuss the possibility of expanding
自由之子的可能性
the Children of Liberty to Europe.
但我觉得你本来计划和菲奥娜住在这里
But I thought you made plans to live here with Fiona.
你当然不是自由代表
Of course you're not Agent Liberty.
因为如果你把我和菲奥娜联系起来
Because if you've connected me to Fiona,
你会知道我在这里的唯一目的就是为她报仇
you know the only reason I'm here is to avenge her.
他永远不会拿这个冒险
And he'd never risk that.
我和我们死去的朋友达成了协议
I made a deal with our dead friend over there
他没有实现
and he did not deliver.
或许你可以
Maybe you can.
谁是自由代表
Who is Agent Liberty?
如果我告诉你  你会让我活命吗
If I tell you, you'll let me live?
我相信不忠应该得到回报
I believe disloyalty should be rewarded.
詹姆斯  拜托  看我啊
James, come on, see me!
我以人类之名这么做
I do this in the name of humanity.
詹姆斯
James!
超女
Supergirl?
詹姆斯
James!
抓住他
Get him!
来吧
Come on!
把他拿下
Take him down!
别动
Don't move!
倒计时开始
Countdown initiated.
二十  十九...
Twenty, nineteen...
我很荣幸结束了这笔交易
I honored my end of the deal.
我交了货
I delivered the goods.
但现在我要把它拿回去
But I think now I'm gonna take it back.
是时候释放笼中之鸟
Time to let our caged bird free.
十  九  八  七
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
六  五...
six, five...
什么  这是什么
What? What's this?
是你的报酬  我们停掉实验了
It's your payment. We're shutting down the experiment.
你可以走了
You're free to go.
等等  为什么
Wait, why?
-我做错什么了吗  -不
- Was it something I did? - No.
没有  我们只是
No, we're just
不再继续了  好吗
not moving forward, okay?
我改变主意了  不值得冒这个险
I've changed my mind. It's not worth the risk.
当然会有风险了
Of course there's risk.
没有风险就没有进步
There's no progress without risk.
我不能再让人死在我手里了  好吗
I just can't have another death on my hands, okay?
不值得
It's not worth it.
我这一生没做过什么有意义的事
I've never done anything meaningful in my life.
而你所做的简直...不可思议
And what you're doing here is... is miraculous.
我参与进来总算给我的人生赋予了意义
If I can be a part of this my life will finally make sense.
好人是不会让别人承担风险的
Good people don't let other people take this kind of risk.
我的肾移植有15%的可能性失败
I have a 15% chance of my kidney transplant not working.
我与风险共存
I live with risk every day.
从古至今  人们愿意
I mean, people risk their lives
为自己的信仰而献出生命
for the things they believe in all the time.
人们入伍打仗  保家卫国
They enlist and go to war to protect their country.
人们当消防员  拯救他人
They become firefighters to save other people.
我所承担的风险是值得的
The risk I'd be taking is worth it to me.
你就是个好人
And you are a good person.
你说过的
You said it yourself,
你能拯救数亿万人
you could save hundreds of millions of people.
有多少人有能力做到这点
How many people can say they have the ability to do that?
你就犯了一个常理之中的错误
So you made one very human mistake
而那时的你几乎还是个小孩
when you were practically a baby.
那不是你的错
That was not your fault.
看看你现在做的所有好事
And look at all the good you're doing now.
求你别剥夺我这个权利
Please don't take this gift away from me.
让我做点儿好事吧
Please let me do something good.
实验对象0331
Subject 0331,
实验一开始
trial one commencement.
谢谢你
Thank you.
今晚你背叛了超女
You betrayed Supergirl tonight.
你背叛了我  你违背了许给菲奥纳的誓言
You betrayed me and your promise to Fiona.
别让复仇蒙蔽了你的灵魂
No vengeance is worth your soul.
灵魂算什么
What soul, old man?
我知道你对菲奥纳的爱  你为她而战的身姿
I saw the love you had for Fiona, how you fought for her.
我也知道你要做什么
I also know what you're gonna do,
我不能让你杀人
and I can't let you kill a man,
即使那个人是自由代表
even if that man is Agent Liberty.
一旦你越界  曼彻斯特  就回不了头了
Once you cross that line, Manchester, there is no going back.
你根本不知道我经历了什么
You have no idea what lines I've already crossed.
感受到了吗
See that there?
那是你的心跳  而我心已死
That's your heart beating. Mine is dead.
每次我闭上眼
And every time I close my eyes
都想听见小菲的声音
and wait to hear Fi's voice,
什么都没有  一片寂静
there's nothing. There's just silence.
我只是躯壳了
I'm empty, man.
那不是真的
That is not true!
你想知道真相吗
You wanna know the truth?
自己看
Look.
为什么还没停
Why won't it stop?
这是共感放大器
It's an empathy amplifier.
专门对抗读心者
It was created to use against empaths,
加倍痛感  锁住一切
double the hurt and keep everything in.
如果我逃不了这种痛  你也一样
If I can't escape this pain, neither can you.
你不该相信我的
You shouldn't have believed in me.
我们已结束了第一次人体实验
We have concluded our first human trial.
实验对象0331展示出了
Test subject 0331 exhibited what could be considered
3分14秒的超人类能力
extra-human powers for precisely three minutes and 14 seconds.
死亡时间  早上4:03
Time of death, 4:03 A.M.
尽管实验对象已死亡
Despite the expiration of the subject,
这项实验还得到了人类基因组最新且关键的信息
the trial reaped new and critical information on the human genome.
未来实验成功率达到87%
Future trials run at an 87% probability of success.
报酬会发给实验对象的家属
Payment will be sent to the subject's next of kin.
我很遗憾  亚当
I'm so sorry, Adam.
我救出了蜘蛛
I moved the spider.
你在忙什么
What you working on?
你知道他们让我对着照相机说了许多
You know, they made me say a lot of things in that camera today.
一些我都不相信的可怕事情
Horrible things that I don't believe in.
我只是想从我的角度
So I just wanna tell my side of the story
谈谈我对自由之子的感受
about my time with the Children of Liberty.
那个事我也想了很多
Yeah, I've been thinking a lot about that, too.
二重性
Duality.
人们总是能给你惊喜
How people can surprise you.
曼彻斯特·布莱克是
Manchester Black is...
是个坏人
is bad.
他杀人  背叛我  但是
He killed people, he betrayed me, but...
但他却帮了我
but then he turned around to help me. I...
也许他不是为了帮你
Well, maybe he wasn't trying to help you.
可能就是巧合罢了
Maybe that was just a consequence.
我猜人们只会展示他们想让你看到的一面
Yeah, I guess people only show you what they want you to see.
而他们不总是那样的
And that's not always who they are.
是的  看看我
Yeah. I mean, look at me, I...
今天我妥协了
I compromised myself today.
你救了汤姆的命
You saved Tom's life.
但我赌上了我所努力的一切
But I risked everything I've worked for.
包括我的名声  我的命
Everything, my reputation, my life.
你的命
Your life.
但是
You know, though,
我想我大概清楚了
I guess I kind of understand
为什么莉娜会隐瞒我地方检察官的事
a little better why Lena lied to me about the DA now.
你应该告诉她的
You should tell her that.
面来了
Pasta is in.
我知道我们上次吵得很不愉快
Look, I know we didn't leave things off on the best note,
我只是
and I was just...
我觉得我们可以再试一次
I was thinking we could try again.
今天好吗
How was your day?
说实话  我很累了
You know what, I'm pretty tired.
做了好多工作
Got a lot of work to do.
那明天见咯
See you tomorrow?
明天见
Tomorrow it is.
我们有什么  这里有几个聪明人
What do we got, a couple of wise guys over here?
出什么事了
What's wrong?
我失败了
I failed.
我错了  我错了
I was wrong. I was wrong.
曼彻斯特
Manchester, uh...
他杀光了那些人
He killed all of them.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
洛克伍德家族钢厂
钢铁制造商